

var questions = [
// question #1
{
topic: `Topic: Captain America: The First Avenger`,
question: `Where does Peggy tell Steve she wants to meet him for a dance before he plunges into the ice?`,
choice: [`The Cotton Club`, `The Stork Club`, `El Morocco`, `The Copacabana` ],
answer: `The Stork Club`
},

// question #2
{
    topic: `Topic: Star Trek: The Next Generation`,
    question: `Where on the Enterprise is Captain Picard when he says the phrase "Make it so" for the first time?`,
    choice: [`The Battle Bridge`, `Captain's Ready Room`, `Main Bridge`, `Main Shuttle Bay` ],
    answer: `The Battle Bridge`
},
    
// question #3
{
    topic: `Topic: `, 
    question: `In Star Wars: Attack of the Clones, the Clone Wars began on which planet?`,
    choice: [`Tatooine`, `Naboo`, `Geonosis`, `Coruscant` ],
    answer: `Geonosis`
},
    
// question #4
{
    topic: `Topic: Batman`, 
    question: `In the Batman comics, which super villain broke Batman's back, leaving him crippled and wheel-chair bound?`,
    choice: [`Ra's Al Ghul`, `Killer Croc`, `Joker`, `Bane`],
    answer: `Bane`
},
    
// question #5
{
    topic: `Topic: Stargate: SG-1`, 
    question: `In Stargate: SG-1, the Tauri (Humans) eventually become "The Fifth Race". Which of the following are not one of the other four races?`,
    choice: [`Alterans`, `Furlings`, `Nox`, `Tagreans` ],
    answer: `Tagreans`
},
    
// question #6
{
    topic: `Topic: Farscape`,
    question: `In Farscape, what is the name of Moya's son?`,
    choice: [`Talon`, `Rygel`, `Scorpius`, `Braca` ],
    answer: `Talon`
},
    
// question #7
{
    topic: `Topic: Back to the future`, 
    question: `In Back to the Future, when Marty travels back in time, he departs from "Twin Pines Mall" in 1985. What mall does he arrive at when he returns back to 1985?`,
    choice: [`Hill Valley Mall`, `Middleton Mall`, `Twin Pines Mall`, `Lone Pine Mall` ],
    answer: `Lone Pine Mall`
},
    
// question #8
{
    topic: `Topic: Battlestar Galactica`, 
    question: `In Battlestar Galactica, which of the following characters never occupies the office of the President of the Colonies?`,
    choice: [`Laura Roslin`, `Tom Zarek`, `Lee Adama`, `Gaius Baltar` ],
    answer: `Tom Zarek`
},
    
// question #9
{
    topic: `Topic: Indiana Jones: Raiders of the Lost Ark`, 
    question: `In Indiana Jones: Raiders of the Lost Ark, who is the main villain?`,
    choice: [`Spalko`, `Toht`, `Belloq`, `Donovan` ],
    answer: `Belloq`
},
    
// question #10
{
    topic: `Topic: Firefly/Serenity`,
    question: `In Firefly/Serenity, when River's subliminal trigger is activated, what name/words does she say?`,
    choice: [`I'm a leaf on the wind`, `Cassandra`, `Miranda`, `two by two, hands of blue` ],
    answer: `Miranda`
}
    


]